Let's update the test insert redv test to use
to use the weather provider to get the weather
query. We'll start by changing the name to test,
insert read provider. So, all we need to do
is take this dv query, and replace it with
the equivalent content provider one, which gets the content
resolver, and then queries the content URI. Now, the
content provider one doesn't take a few of these parameters.
For example, it doesn't take TABLE_NAME, because that's implied
by the URI, nor does it support group by.
The rest of it should work pretty well. Now,
let's run the test and verify that it passes.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
And the test still passes. [LAUGH] Again, it's very easy to substitute
out something that calls directly to the database with a content provider.